[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many horns does the Indian Rhinoceros, found only in Asia, have on its snout?", "correct_answer": "One", "incorrect_answers": ["None", "Two", "Three"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does C.W. Ettingers book Man into Superman deal with?", "correct_answer": "Cryogenics", "incorrect_answers": ["Putting computers into humans", "Transplanting animal organs into humans", "Transplanting human organs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sonnys partner was killed by  the police at the end of the movie Dog Day Afternoon?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Simon says, generally a childrens game of concentration and quick reactions, appears in which of these action-packed movies?", "correct_answer": "The Die Hard series", "incorrect_answers": ["The James Bond series", "Cobra", "Speed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which film company released the movie House of 1000 Corpses?", "correct_answer": "Lion Gate Films", "incorrect_answers": ["Paramount", "MGM", "Walt Disney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Extract from the Periwinkle plant is one of the worlds most powerful drugs, used to fight this disease.", "correct_answer": "Cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Hepatitis B", "AIDS", "Psoriosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nectarines are often mistakenly thought to be a crossbreed between peaches and these fruits.", "correct_answer": "Plums", "incorrect_answers": ["Wild apples", "Apricots", "Pears"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Eve of Destruction, this actor played the aging father of Eve, Bill Simmons, who was hunted down by the robot Eve because of the way he treated Eves mother.", "correct_answer": "Kevin McCarthy", "incorrect_answers": ["Abe Vigoda", "Richard Crenna", "David Wayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the smallest of the three waterfalls that make up the Niagara Falls.", "correct_answer": "Bridal Veil Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["There are only two waterfalls that make up the Niagara Falls.", "Goat Falls", "Horseshoe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Absinthe was prohibited in this year, because it was believed to be reason for elevated crime rates.", "correct_answer": "1915", "incorrect_answers": ["1919", "1961", "1906"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many bones does the human spine have?", "correct_answer": "33", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "12", "48"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the Earths water is fresh water?", "correct_answer": "less than 5%", "incorrect_answers": ["between 13% and 20%", "between 5% and 11%", "between 20% and 22.4%"]}]